Nicholas Lee

Agile Coach and Software Engineer in Test with 12 years experience in both automated and manual testing environments. Agility is paramount. I have a genuine passion for Agile development, people and teams, and I constantly seek improvement in the work that I do and in myself.

395 Collins St Melbourne, VIC 3000 (04) 16 292 302 nicholas.l.lee@outlook.com

EXPERIENCE

Zendesk, Melbourne — Agile Coach

April 2020 - April 2021

I worked closely with four different software engineering teams and their leadership, facilitating Scrum rituals and offering coaching and mentoring where required. I gathered and analysed key pieces of data of the teams' deliverables, offering suggestions to promote growth in the efficiency of delivery.

Zendesk, Melbourne — Senior Software Engineer in Test

November 2016 - PRESENT

I conduct the activities and procedures relating to quality, for several software development teams. I assist in the coaching of their testing techniques and Agile practises.

Reece Group, Melbourne — Test Analyst Team Lead

October 2014 - November 2016

As Team Lead, I was responsible for recruitment and for the wellbeing of the testing team. I also like to keep up to date with the tools and trends of modern day testing and offer mentoring..

Reece Group, Melbourne — Test Analyst

February 2009 - October 2014

I worked with a number of different teams, doing Agile project work. Roles included test analysis and development, Scrum Mastery, active SME.

EDUCATION

Swinburne University, Lilydale — Bachelor of Applied Science in Information Technology

January 2001 - October 2004

LANGUAGES

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Ruby

FRAMEWORKS

Gatsby

Jekyll

React

Bootstrap CSS

Bulma CSS

Tailwind

TOOLS

VSCode, Atom

Node.js

MySQL

Git

jQuery

AJAX